skunkstudios.com 2005-04-03

# Skunk Studios * Privacy Policy

## Skunk Studios Privacy Policy

Skunk Studios takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**  

  * This Privacy Policy covers Skunk Studios's treatment of personally identifiable information that Skunk Studios collects when you are on the Skunk Studios site, and when you use Skunk Studios's services. This policy also covers Skunk Studios's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Skunk Studios's business partners share with Skunk Studios or that Skunk Studios may collect on a partner's site. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Skunk Studios does not own or control, or to people that Skunk Studios does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**  

  * Skunk Studios collects personally identifiable information when you register a Skunk Studios product, when you use certain Skunk Studios products or services, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Skunk Studios may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 
  * When you register with Skunk Studios, we ask for your email address, age, gender, and zip code. 
  * Skunk Studios also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Skunk Studios cookie information and the page you requested. 
  * Skunk Studios uses information for three general purposes: to customize the content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * Skunk Studios will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. This information is used solely by Skunk Studios and will not be sold to, or used by, any third party. 

**Cookies**  

> Skunk Studios may set and access Skunk Studios cookies on your computer. A cookie is a text file with user information entered while using our products or services. 

**Security**  

In certain areas Skunk Studios uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 
**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

> Skunk Studios may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

**Questions or Suggestions**  

> If you have questions or suggestions, please email us at contact@skunkstudios.com. 

**Skunk Studios™
